(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{23:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},38:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(52)},43:function(e,t,n){},44:function(e,t,n){},45:function(e,t,n){},51:function(e,t,n){},52:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),o=n(11),i=n.n(o),c=(n(43),n(44),n(29)),s=n(30),l=n(34),u=n(33),m=n(23),d=n(24),h=n(75),y=n(7),p=n(85),f=n(77),w=n(81),g=n(78),_=n(80),E=n(82),q=n(79),v=n(9),b=n.n(v),C=n(10),S=n.n(C),A=n(84),F=(n(45),Object(h.a)({root:{width:700,minHeight:350,maxHeight:400,textAlign:"left",padding:50},question:{color:"black",fontSize:"2rem"},progressRoot:{height:10,backgroundColor:Object(y.d)("#ff6c5c",.5),borderRadius:20},bar:{height:16,borderRadius:20}}));function k(e){var t=e.question,n=e.nextQuestion,o=e.total,i=e.questionNo,c=e.progress,s=e.checkUserAnswer,l=e.maxScore,u=e.score,m=Object(a.useState)(""),h=Object(d.a)(m,2),y=h[0],v=h[1],C=Object(a.useState)(""),k=Object(d.a)(C,2),x=k[0],R=k[1],H=function(e){v(e),s(e),decodeURIComponent(t.correct_answer)==e?R("Correct!"):R("InCorrect!")};var W=F();return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:W.progressRoot},r.a.createElement(A.a,{className:W.bar,variant:"determinate",color:"secondary",value:c})),r.a.createElement(p.a,{className:W.root},r.a.createElement(f.a,null,r.a.createElement(g.a,null,r.a.createElement(q.a,{variant:"h5",component:"h3"},"Question ",i," of ",o),r.a.createElement(q.a,{gutterBottom:!0,variant:"body2",color:"textSecondary",component:"p"},decodeURIComponent(t.category)),"hard"===t.difficulty?r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(b.a,null),r.a.createElement(b.a,null),r.a.createElement(b.a,null)):"medium"===t.difficulty?r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(b.a,null),r.a.createElement(b.a,null),r.a.createElement(S.a,null)):"easy"===t.difficulty?r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(b.a,null),r.a.createElement(S.a,null),r.a.createElement(S.a,null)):r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(S.a,null),r.a.createElement(S.a,null),r.a.createElement(S.a,null)),r.a.createElement(_.a,null),r.a.createElement(q.a,{variant:"body1",color:"textSecondary",component:"p",className:W.question},decodeURIComponent(t.question)))),r.a.createElement(w.a,null,t.incorrect_answers.map((function(e){return r.a.createElement(E.a,{variant:y===decodeURIComponent(e)?"contained":"outlined",color:"primary",key:decodeURIComponent(e),onClick:function(){return H(decodeURIComponent(e))},disabled:""!==y},decodeURIComponent(e))})),r.a.createElement(E.a,{variant:y===decodeURIComponent(t.correct_answer)?"contained":"outlined",color:"primary",key:decodeURIComponent(t.correct_answer),onClick:function(){return H(decodeURIComponent(t.correct_answer))},disabled:""!==y},decodeURIComponent(t.correct_answer))),r.a.createElement(q.a,{variant:"h5",component:"h3",className:"message"},y&&x),""!==y&&100!==c?r.a.createElement(E.a,{variant:"contained",className:"next-button",color:"secondary",key:"next",onClick:function(){n(),v("")}},"Next Question"):""),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-wrapper"},r.a.createElement("p",null,"Score: ",u," %"),r.a.createElement("p",null,"MaxScore: ",l," %")),r.a.createElement("div",{className:W.progressRoot},r.a.createElement(A.a,{className:W.bar,variant:"determinate",color:"secondary",value:u,valueBuffer:l})))}n(51);var x=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(){var e;Object(c.a)(this,n);for(var a=arguments.length,r=new Array(a),o=0;o<a;o++)r[o]=arguments[o];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(r))).state={questions:m,current_question:null,current_question_no:1,total_question_no:m.length,progress:5,score:0,maxScore:0,currectAnswered:0,wrongAnswered:0},e.nextQuestion=function(){var t=e.state.current_question_no+1;t<=e.state.total_question_no&&(e.setState({current_question_no:t}),e.setState({current_question:e.state.questions[t-1]}),e.setState({progress:t/e.state.total_question_no*100}))},e.checkUserAnswer=function(t){var n=e.state,a=n.current_question,r=n.current_question_no,o=n.currectAnswered,i=n.wrongAnswered,c=n.total_question_no;if(decodeURIComponent(a.correct_answer)==t){e.setState({currectAnswered:o+1});var s=((o+1)/r*100).toFixed(2);e.setState({score:s})}else{e.setState({wrongAnswered:i+1});var l=(o/r*100).toFixed(2);e.setState({score:l})}var u=(r/c*100).toFixed(2);e.setState({maxScore:u})},e}return Object(s.a)(n,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.setState({current_question:this.state.questions[0]})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-panel-wrapper"},null!==this.state.current_question?r.a.createElement(k,{question:this.state.current_question,nextQuestion:this.nextQuestion,total:this.state.total_question_no,questionNo:this.state.current_question_no,progress:this.state.progress,checkUserAnswer:this.checkUserAnswer,maxScore:this.state.maxScore,score:this.state.score}):"")}}]),n}(a.Component),R=n(32),H=n(83),W=Object(R.a)({palette:{primary:{light:"#fff",main:"#e7643d",dark:"#000"},secondary:{main:"#f44336"}},typography:{useNextVariants:!0}});var I=function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement(H.a,{theme:W},r.a.createElement(x,null)))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(I,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}},[[38,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2d3d820a.chunk.js.map